♪♪
You'll... You're gonna
be all right! You're all right!
Come on, come on.
Whoa!
Whoa. Geez, this
thing weighs a ton.
What's the occasion?
We got something new in.
You call this new?
- Ross.
- Hmm?
Remember those Hawks
tickets I said I might
- be able to get you?
- Yeah.
That's great.
That's really nice. Thank you.
Ah. The new suits
finally came in, huh?
Nice, huh?
Very nice.
Reminds me of the suit
they buried my grandfather in.
Sid's all right.
He can't help it if he
lives in a time warp.
- Ben?
- Yeah?
Good to see you.
- Oh, hi, Ross. How you doing?
- Good.
Help you find something?
Well, as a matter of fact,
I was thinking about
buying a new suit.
- No kidding.
- Yeah.
Hey, you talk about timing.
We just got something in.
Here, let me show it to you.
Huh?
Oh, it's you, Ben.
Feel it.
Nothing like the look and feel
of genuine gabardine, is there?
No, no, there isn't.
Oh, th... oh, that's-that's it.
That's it!
Hey, Sid.
I pulled it out as soon
as I heard your voice.
- Oh...
- What do you think?
Oh, I think you got a sale.
I'm sure we have your
measurements on file,
but let me get Enrico
out here just to make sure.
Okay. Uh... Sid?
Do you think you could
throw in a couple
of pairs of socks?
Hello, Ben. Ben Matlock.
Hey, Marv.
Hey.
How are you?
I'm fine. What do you think?
- Oh, that's beautiful.
- Yeah.
Beautiful.
You're supposed to be
inventorying shirts, aren't you?
Right away.
Yes.
What's this I hear about
your daughter getting married?
Oh, yeah, this Saturday.
Would you believe?
That's if he doesn't
get cold feet.
That's if my checks
don't bounce.
Either of which
is quite possible.
My oldest, most
favorite customer.
Oh, Enrico.
Enrico will check
your measurements
- and get right to work.
- Oh, good.
How does Monday sound?
Monday? You don't have
to rush on my account.
It's no rush.
No problem.
Please, step up.
Okay. Excuse me.
Yeah, Ben, I'm gonna
leave you with Enrico.
Sid and I have some
business to talk about.
I was just at the bank.
Yeah?
You ask them about the loan?
No, I went in there to
buy a couple of CDs.
Of course I asked
them about the loan.
They turned us down.
We'll just go somewhere else.
We'll just get turned
down somewhere else.
How we gonna make
the payroll next week?
How we gonna pay the rent?
Face it, Sid.
We're not.
So now what?
Bankruptcy?
There's another option.
What?
Well, we have insurance.
The people who own the building,
they have insurance.
So?
So we hire some guy
to torch the place and
we collect the insurance.
We start over again.
- You can't be serious.
- Yeah.
I'm dead serious.
I've given this
a lot of thought.
We'll get caught.
Well, George Clancy
didn't get caught.
But that was an accident.
No, it wasn't.
No accident.
That fire was set.
What if somebody gets hurt?
Nobody was hurt in
George Clancy's fire.
My God, Marv.
This is our business.
We started it, we built it.
We put 32 years
of our life into it,
and now you want to destroy it?
Oh... Damn it, will
you open your eyes?
It is destroyed!
It's gone, Sid, it's gone.
We can either let the
creditors pick over the bones,
or we can use
what little we got left
and make it work for us.
George Clancy's
over in the mall.
He's selling more
shoes than he ever did.
It's wrong.
He gave me the name
of the guy he used.
We can talk to him. Hmm?
Talk.
Okay?
He's not gonna show.
Let's get back to the store.
He'll show, he'll show.
Sit down.
Probably casing us right now.
Be sure that we're
not cops or something.
You mean, the police
are looking for this guy?
We're gonna be associating
with a known felon?
Sid, will you relax?
Relax?
What if the police
are casing him?
Mr. Shea?
Yeah. I'm Marv Shea.
Al Brown.
You mind if I sit down?
No, sit down.
Sid Franklin, my partner.
Mr. Franklin, nice to meet you.
You know, you fellas have
got a very nice little store.
Two stories, nice big
window out in front.
Two more in the rear.
Couple of rooms in the back.
Incidentally, how many are
there in the back, two or three?
That was difficult to tell.
Three. Three back there.
There's the office and
a sewing room and-and
a bathroom.
Ah, that's good, that's good.
You-You got a gas furnace?
Downstairs.
You were in the store?
This morning.
I was there from 8:30
on; I didn't see you.
Mr. Franklin, I didn't
want you to see me.
Now, when would
you like it to be done?
This Saturday night.
Your daughter's getting
married this Saturday night.
Yeah, I know. That's
why, that's why.
Store'll be empty.
Everybody will
be at the reception.
How much?
$40,000.
15 before, 20 after
and five right now.
That's the earnest money
that we talked about.
Wait a minute.
You didn't say anything
about giving him money.
Mr. Shea, Mr. Franklin,
thank you very much.
I will be in touch.
No, that's fine.
No, I understand.
I understand. That's...
I thought it over, Marv.
Yeah, what?
Yeah, 9:30. I'll be waiting.
I can't let you do this.
We built every inch of this
business honestly and fairly.
And I'd just as soon
lose it honestly and fairly
than see it burned to the ground
- Sid...
- by some criminal!
Sid, it is done!
That was him on the phone.
Now, listen.
Saturday night,
9:30, I am going to
leave the reception.
I'm going to meet him in the
alley right behind the ballroom.
I'm going to give
him some money.
- No.
- He's going to
come back here and he's
going to burn this place down,
and we are going to
have something to show
for 32 years of sweat.
No!
Sid... we declare bankruptcy,
we are never going
to get out from under it.
You understand that?
We are too damn old!
Now, I'm not going to
spend the rest of my life
living off of the government.
Or what's worse,
living off of my kids.
Sid, collecting
on the insurance,
that's the only way out for us.
God help us.
God help us, Marv.
Where's your date?
Didn't bring one.
Have you thought about it?
Are you still planning to do it?
Of course.
Marv, think.
Think about her.
If something went
wrong and we got caught
and sent to prison, it
would kill your daughter.
You just can't risk it, Marv.
Why don't we meet with
Mr. Brown and tell him the deal is off?
You nuts or what?
Please, Marv.
Try to get the 5,000 back.
Look, I don't know what
we'll do about the store,
but we just can't go to jail.
I'll go with you, if you like.
Forget it.
Marv?
Oh!
Oh! Oh, Marv!
Hey, what's going on back here?!
Huh?
Don't move, man!
Hold it right there!
Well, I didn't like the idea of
Marv being with some kind
of a fugitive all by himself,
so I followed him.
I heard something, and...
went to take a look,
and there he was.
Oh.
Did you see anybody
else in the alley at all?
No.
But it had to be
the arsonist, Ben.
Marv had $15,000 on him.
Last thing I said to
him was, "Think about it.
It's not too late."
You know, maybe he
did change his mind
and put up a fuss,
and then the guy stabbed
him, grabbed the money,
and he took off when
he heard me coming.
What'd you say
this fellow's name is?
Al Brown.
George Clancy recommended him.
He was the guy that burned
his old shoe store down.
Mmm.
Marv and I were partners,
Ben, and we didn't always agree,
and sometimes we
fought over things, but...
He was real cheap, you know?
Oh, I know he was.
But... why would I kill him?
Enrico overheard that
argument between the two of you
the other night in the office.
And he told the D.A. that
you were very, very
mad at Marv... I was.
I swear to you,
Ben... I didn't kill him.
I know.
I believe you.
I've been a satisfied
customer of yours for 20 years.
And I'm gonna do
my very best for you.
Al Brown?
Probably an alias.
How am I supposed to find him?
Same way Marv Shea
did; through George Clancy.
Mr. Matlock, you haven't
touched your eggs.
Uh, no, ma'am, I'm just
having coffee this morning.
George Clancy has a
brand-new shoe store in the mall.
The old shoe store burned down.
MRS. McCARDLE:
Anything wrong with 'em?
With...? Oh, oh...
no, oh, no, no!
I'm just kinda,
kinda watching it.
Your client ever see
this Al Brown guy?
Yeah, he's, uh, medium
height, late 40s, grayish hair.
That's about it.
He's got an accomplice,
but, uh, Sid didn't
get a good look at him.
I've always cooked my
scrambled eggs that way.
Nice and fluffy and a
bit on the loose side.
M-Mrs. McCardle,
I'm-I'm sure your eggs
are, are, are wonderful,
but the fact is
I-I had a fitting
for a new suit the other day
and it was a
little, a little tight.
It's not, not that I've gained.
My late husband
William loved my eggs.
"Mary Katherine," he'd say,
"you've done it again."
He was a darlin' man, darlin'.
Darlin', yeah.
Just-Just for a few
days, and-and then...
It was a pleasure
cooking for a man like that.
Ah, he could stuff his face.
Well, m-maybe on the
weekend we could...
I'll bet that if he
was here right now,
he'd know what to
do with those eggs.
He'd dig in.
Mrs. McCardle?
Mrs. McCardle, look.
Look, Mrs. McCardle.
Mmm!
Good eggs!
Mmm-mmm!
Oh, that's so beautiful.
Well, perhaps since you're
here, you should try it on.
Oh, that's a good idea...
Here, here, here, here.
All right.
Just give me that
beauty. Ha-ha-ha.
Uh-huh.
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha.
You've been working at this
store as long as I can remember.
Oh, uh, since the
first day it opened.
Yeah. It must have
been quite a shock
when you heard Marv say
he was gonna burn it down.
It was an outrage.
It made me furious.
It made all of us furious.
What do you mean, "all of us"?
All of us: me,
Sid, Ross, Cheryl.
How did Ross and
Cheryl find out about it?
I told them.
How could I keep something
so horrible to myself?
Ah, how does it feel?
Perfect.
Uh-huh.
Maybe just a little
tight right through there.
Oh? A little tight?
It's a miracle you can breathe.
Have you gained weight?
No!
Gained weight!
I'm very careful.
Look at that.
You sure this is the same cut?
There's only one cut.
Go right back in there
and take them off.
Enrico will fix.
Gained weight.
Your sewing machine
probably zigged
when it was supposed to zag.
Those in the brown, but...
Well, I brought
a brown pair out.
Hi. Uh, my salesman said
you wanted to talk to me.
George Clancy?
That's right.
I like this place better
than your old place.
Oh, thank you.
Must have collected a lot of
money on your fire insurance
to pay for this
kind of lease, huh?
What do you want?
Name is Conrad McMasters.
I have a friend who has a
little restaurant downtown.
Losing his shirt, so
he's interested in doing
to his place what you
did to your old place.
Hey, this is a shoe store.
You want shoes, I can help you.
You want something
else, I can't help you.
Okay. You got this in brown?
Brown?
Yeah, brown, as in Al Brown?
Who'd you say you were?
Just somebody who's looking
to retain his
services, that's all.
Well...
Ben! Hey, you got
the new suit on, huh?
Looks great.
Uh, well, actually,
this is my old suit.
Enrico's still working
on the new one.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen, Ben... Mm-hmm?
How's Sid doing?
Pretty good.
He's out on bail.
I sent him home
to get some rest.
I can't believe anybody would
think he committed murder.
Yeah.
- He's the most decent guy I know.
- Hmm...
I hear you knew that
Marv was gonna go talk
to the arsonist that night.
Yeah, I knew.
Did you happen to notice
if anybody left when he did?
I didn't even see him leave.
Next thing you know,
the police showed up.
I thought they were gonna
say the store had burned down,
not that Marv had been murdered.
Oh.
Tell me the truth, Ben.
Are you gonna be
able to get Sid off?
I'm gonna give him my best shot.
You Conrad?
Yeah. Who are you?
Al Brown.
You're not Al Brown.
How do you know?
I know what Al Brown looks like.
AI's a busy man.
I do his research.
And if you don't like
it, hey, it's been real.
Wait! Hey!
All right... the restaurant's
at 1715 Hightower.
It's called the
Rio Bar and Grill.
My friend wants it done
before the end of the week.
I'll look it over
tonight, talk to Al
and get back to
you with an estimate.
Is that okay by you?
No money till I talk to the man.
He wouldn't have
it any other way.
Uh, hey, Cheryl, I-I've
been looking for you.
I'm missing an invoice.
I can't find it.
Oh... oh, have-have-have
you got a few minutes to talk?
As a matter of fact, I don't.
I told Marv's wife I'd stop by
and help her with the
funeral arrangements.
T-Tomorrow, maybe?
Uh, sure.
Yeah. Tomorrow, maybe...
Tomorrow, maybe...
♪♪
Hey!
Oh...
Can you describe the
man you were following?
Yeah, uh... 5'9",
thin, red hair, wearing
a blue jogging suit.
Conrad, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. They were
just trying to scare me, I think.
Doors were locked
from the outside.
They were trying to kill you.
Who's "they"?
The arsonist who
probably killed Marvin Shea.
You feel like looking
at some mug shots?
Damn right.
I want to get these guys.
Oh, no. Ross!
- Oh, I got it. I got it.
- Oh! Thanks.
- I got it. I got it, I...
- Thanks.
Guess I should
have made two trips.
Ross isn't here.
Sid gave him the day off.
I just stopped by to
pick up my new suit.
Oh, well, you want
me to get it for you?
En-Enrico already
did. I-I'm wearing it.
Oh! Well, it looks nice.
Thanks.
Thinning.
Well... Oh, I was, um...
I was, um, poking around in-in
Marv's office the other day...
Uh, yesterday, after you left...
And-and I found this in...
way back in one of his drawers.
Why would Marv have a clipping
from a hit-and-run
three years ago?
I was gonna ask you.
- I have no idea.
- Oh.
Did you ask Sid?
He didn't know, either.
Huh... So, um... you were, uh...
you were at the reception
the other night, huh?
You bet.
Anything I can get off that
man free and not work 14 hours?
I was for that.
Yeah.
Marv was cheap, all right.
So you were there.
Along with 100 other people,
stashing it away, just like me.
Did, uh, did you stay in
the ballroom the whole time?
Yes.
With your husband?
Well, I hung out
with a lot of people.
With Enrico and
his family, and Ross.
Come to think of it,
he wasn't there the whole night.
Who?
Ross.
I wanted to introduce him
to this girl that
I was talking to,
but I couldn't find him.
Seems it was right around 9:30.
Well, hi, Ben.
Ross. Can I talk
to you for a minute?
Sure. Yeah. Come
on in and sit down.
Okay. Okay.
Can I get you
something to drink?
- Nah.
- It'll have to be something soft.
I've been on the wagon
for a couple of years.
That's right.
You used to put it away
pretty good, didn't you?
Oh, yeah. But that's over.
What, did you just quit?
Yeah. It wasn't hard.
Huh.
So...
You lied to me.
Excuse me?
You left the
reception that night.
How come?
Mm-hmm. All right.
Mr. Matlock?
Mr. Matlock...
Mrs. McCardle, what
are you doing here?
Your lunch. You went
off without breakfast,
and you've got to have
something if you're going
to be arguing with judges
and killers and the like.
Now, why don't you sit right
down here on this bench?
Now, this was my late
husband's favorite lunch.
A meat loaf sandwich
with a slice of onion
and a garlic pickle.
He'd say, "Mary Katherine,
you've done it again."
Oh, yeah.
Well, I've worlds of
work to do, so enjoy.
Ta-ta!
His lunch.
It's a meat loaf sandwich
with a slice of onion
and a garlic pickle.
Well, good-bye.
Mr. Gordon,
would you please tell
the court what you saw
the night Marvin
Shea was murdered?
Well, I was at his
daughter's wedding reception,
along with him and
all the other guests,
when, around 9:30, I saw him
slip out one of the side doors,
so I followed him.
Why did you follow him?
Well, because Enrico,
the tailor at the store,
had told me that Marv planned
to leave the party and meet with
the arsonist who was
going to burn down the store.
Well, I went after him because
I wanted to stop him somehow.
Make him see that what
he was doing was wrong.
Yeah.
Well, did you stop him?
No.
By the time I got to the alley,
he was already
talking to the guy.
So I just hung back and watched.
I saw him hand the
guy an envelope.
A-And then it sounded like he
was demanding more money.
The next thing I knew,
the other guy had
a knife in his hand,
and Marv was
struggling with him.
Finally... the guy
raised his hand
and brought it down
in Marv's chest.
Marv went down...
and the guy took off.
What'd this man look like?
Medium height... longish hair...
That's about all I could see.
Well, I-I didn't get a
good look at his face.
It was too dark.
Sure it wasn't the defendant?
Positive.
You said it was dark.
Well, you don't have
to see someone's face
to know who they are.
Well, you can
tell by their build...
the way they
move, their clothes.
Now, I've worked for
Sid Franklin for five years.
And the man that I saw in
that alley that night was not him.
I am absolutely, 100% positive.
Uh, Mr. Gordon,
why did you wait?
Why didn't you come forward
with, uh, your story right away?
Because I figured if the man
that I saw killed Marvin Shea,
he'd have no qualms
about killing me.
I'm not much of a hero.
I was afraid.
Yeah.
Thank you, Mr. Gordon.
Mr. Burgess.
No questions, Your Honor.
Witness may step down.
So, where are we now?
Well, if we can find this Al
Brown, we're in business.
Hello, Petey.
What's up?
You know that guy that wanted
you to torch that restaurant?
The guy who didn't check out?
The guy you took care of.
Yeah.
Well, I was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
Al!
It's so nice to
finally meet you.
Pete has told me
so much about you.
He's also told Lieutenant
Lasky over there...
Uh, Sergeant Powell...
Sergeant Deko, and...
Officer Evans over there.
They made me a deal.
Let's go, Mr. Brown.
Well, come on in, Ben.
Meet Marvin Latham,
otherwise known as Al Brown.
I'm Ben Matlock,
defense attorney
in the Marvin Shea case.
Pleasure to meet you.
Likewise, I'm sure.
Is, uh, is your lawyer here?
No.
No, the fact is, I'm doing
just fine without one.
He's agreed to talk about the
Marvin Shea case in exchange
for our dropping one
charge of arson against him.
- Is it all right if I...?
- No, no.
Please, be my guest.
Um, I understand that
Marvin Shea arranged for you
to burn down his clothing store.
That's right.
And, uh, you arranged for him
to meet you in the alley in
back of the Kingston Hotel
to get your down payment.
That's right.
And you met him there
and, uh, found that he was,
uh, backing out of the deal,
and argued with him
and stabbed him to death.
Oh, no, no, no.
Now, that's not right.
It's not?
No.
I never made the meeting.
Oh, come on.
I had flown to
Chicago the day before.
On business.
Furniture store
out in Lincolnwood
went up in flames that night.
Really?
Boy.
That is some
coincidence, isn't it?
Anyway, they had, uh,
closed the airport
because of foul weather
for four hours the next day.
Really screwed
up all the flights.
Just about the time
that I was supposed
to be meeting Mr. Marvin
Shea in that alleyway,
I was actually flying
over Tennessee.
That's a lie.
You were seen arguing with
him, and you were seen killing him.
I'm sorry.
Well, show him.
We found this in his pocket.
It's a ticket stub.
His flight to and from Chicago.
He was on the plane, Ben.
I keep very meticulous records.
You know, for tax purposes.
Ben, your witness lied.
He lied, and I traded off
an arson charge for nothing.
No!
I didn't lie to protect myself.
Look, I was trying to help Sid.
By committing perjury?
Sid is a good guy.
And Marv was a creep.
It isn't right that
Sid should suffer
just because Marv finally
got what he deserved.
Ross... I want you
to tell me something.
Did you do any
drinking that night?
I never had a drop.
Well, I quit on August 25, 1988,
and I haven't had a drop since.
Ben...?
Ben...!
Mr. Matlock.
Oh, hello, Cheryl.
I was just in here
poking around to
see what I could find.
Oh, uh, you must be Mrs. Shea.
My condolences.
I'm Ben Matlock,
uh, Sid's lawyer.
How do you do?
She came to pick
up Marv's things.
Oh, is there anything
I can do to help you?
No.
Oh, are these the
wedding pictures?
I got them yesterday.
I thought you might
like to see them.
Oh, your daughter
looks so beautiful.
And Marv... never
looked so happy.
Look, he's even got
his arm around Ross.
Uh... uh, c-could...
could-could I just look
at those for a minute?
Sure.
Why not?
Thank you.
I love to look at
we-wedding pictures.
Oh, they're having...
some swell time.
Well...
I recalled you to the
stand, Mr. Gordon,
because... the other day,
you didn't exactly tell
the whole truth, did you?
No, sir.
Yeah. Well, now, if you
can tell the whole truth today,
maybe... just-just maybe...
The district attorney
won't file perjury
charges against you.
You think you can
- tell the truth today?
- Yes, sir, I can.
Good, good.
Now, uh, before we...
before we start talking
about, uh, what happened
the night Marvin
Shea was killed,
let's talk about what happened
the night of August 24, 1988.
I'm... afraid you lost me.
Well... the night
of August 24, 1988,
a man and woman were killed
in an automobile accident
out on the Old Ridge Road.
A hit-and-run driver
forced their car off the road
and into a tree, and witnesses
at the scene say
that hit-and-run driver
had to be drunk.
I-I'm sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Of course you do.
And if Marvin Shea were here,
he'd know, too, wouldn't he?
I found this hidden
away, way in the back
of one of the
drawers in his desk.
See?
You didn't know he
had that, did you?
See that?
Hit-and-run.
He kept this... because...
he knew that drunk
driver was you, didn't he?
That's not true.
Mm-hmm.
You used to drink
quite a lot, didn't you?
I don't drink.
Yeah, but years
ago, you used to...
you used to put it down
pretty good, didn't you?
Yes.
When did you get sober?
Close to three years.
You got sober August 25, 1988,
the day after the accident.
And you got sober
because you knew your drinking
had killed two innocent people.
No!
Witnesses...
say that that hit-and-run
car was dark in color,
four-door sedan.
You used to drive a
car like that, didn't you?
- Well, yes.
- And you sold that
car two and a half weeks
after the accident, didn't you?
I-I don't remember.
Uh-huh.
Where did you take
the car to get it repaired?
Your Honor, we fail to
see the relevancy of this
- line of questioning.
- Relevance?!
I found where he took
the car to have it repaired,
and traces of green
paint were found
on the right-hand
side of that car, and the
car that was run off
the road was green.
Overruled. Mr. Matlock,
- please get on with it.
- Yes, sir.
Somehow...
Marvin Shea knew you were
that drunk hit-and-run driver,
but he didn't say anything;
he kept quiet about it.
And you didn't go to prison...
As long as you kept up...
a little arrangement.
Like, uh...
taking home... half commissions.
No, that's not true.
He worked you
unreasonable hours,
and you took home
less than half the pay
the other salesmen took home.
And you even worked at
his house on weekends.
But you did it because you
knew that, at any moment,
he could pull the
string and destroy you.
So you put up with his
insults, his cheapness,
the horrible way he treated you.
Well, you got tired of it,
found an opportunity,
and killed him.
No!
Yes, you did.
These are copies...
Here you go...
of some photographs
that were taken...
at the party the
night he was killed.
In this first one, he
was still alive, see?
There's you next to
him and his daughter
and the rest of the
people from the store.
This one was taken
after he was killed.
Uh, it's hard to see,
but that clock says 9:50.
Can you see that? Yeah.
The security guard
who found the body
called the police at 9:40.
That means this picture
had to have been made
just moments before
the police arrived.
- I suppose so.
- Yeah.
The odd thing is...
you're wearing...
two different ties.
Look at this. Look at this.
He's wearing two different ties.
You changed ties in
the middle of the party.
How come?
And what-what's even odder...
is this tie that you're
wearing in this second picture
is exactly like the
tie Marv was wearing.
You see that?
How do you explain that?
Well... I went out and rented...
two tuxedo ties...
exactly like the
ones in that picture.
See that?
And-And you know
something about clothes...
They're easy to take off
and put on, aren't they?
- Yeah.
- Well... how about this?
You left the party
shortly before Marv did,
waited for him...
and when he walked
out into that alley
you jumped up and stabbed him!
And he grabbed
that knife in his chest,
and then he grabbed
at you! That's right!
And all he could
touch was your tie.
Run!
Run! And that's what
you would've done, run.
But you realized...
he had blood on his hands,
and there'd be
blood on your tie.
So that's why...
when you came
back into that party...
you were wearing Marv's tie.
And I have one more
photograph that proves it.
The coroner's
photograph... of Marv.
See?
He's wearing the
tie you were wearing
in that first picture.
See, I remembered
this coroner's picture,
and I remembered
the blood on the tie,
these pictures of you,
and it really wasn't hard
to figure out...
how the blood got on that tie.
We find the
defendant not guilty.
Hey, Ben! You made it!
Business is
certainly picking up!
Oh, it's been this way
ever since the trial.
I guess it was
all that publicity.
Come over here; I want
to show you something.
Huh?
Our new salesman's
got lots of great ideas.
He wants to update our lines
and stop carrying the
slower-moving suits.
Uh... you-you don't
mean... I'm afraid so.
But this is the only
place I can get 'em,
and if I have to have
'em custom-made,
it'll cost me an arm and a
leg... What am I gonna do?
You're gonna have to
stock up, that's what.
www.tvsubtitles.net